COLE WORSLEY

SUMMARY

I am a hard working front end web developer with a passion for learning. I have a well-rounded foundation in test driven development and object oriented programming. I'm driven to work with a strong development team to learn and grow as well as create a quality product. With a background in financial analytics, I also bring strong business experience and attention to detail.

PROJECTS

Weatherly

Project built on React.js using the Weather Underground API to display a detailed weather forecast. For this project, I implemented asynchronous javascript to load various components and information onto the page. It also includes a custom built prefix search trie to load different locations.

EDUCATION

Turing School of Software and Design

Certificate of Web Application Development Front End Engineering 2017

University of Denver

BS Finance 2013

Awarded the Brad Busse full endowed scholarship for exemplary performance as a division one swimmer and as a student.

EMPLOYMENT

Centura Health Physician Group, *Sr. Financial Analyst*, Denver, CO Aug 2016 - Mar 2017 Responsible for tracking growth and communicating results to hospital leadership for entire north Denver region.

Financial Analyst, Denver, CO

Sep 2013 - Aug 2016

Utilize excel and VBA to design and build reporting package for physician group financial and operational analysis.

Credit Analyst Intern, Denver, CO

Jun 2013 - Sep 2013

Developed a business acumen in teamwork and communication along with a fundamental understanding of Microsoft Excel and the use of information systems attributed to Electronic Medical Records.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JavaScript (ES6), React/Redux, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Node, Express, Sketch, Excel VBA